{"id": "VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_5::VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_1.jpg::Justice:Arrest-Jail", "sentence_id": "VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_5", "image": "VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_1.jpg", "image_stem": "VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_1", "event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "text": "Two Chicago police officers take a man into custody during a protest march, Wednesday, Nov. 25, 2015, in Chicago, the day after murder charges were brought against police officer Jason Van Dyke in the killing of 17-year-old Laquan McDonald", "words": ["Two", "Chicago", "police", "officers", "take", "a", "man", "into", "custody", "during", "a", "protest", "march", ",", "Wednesday", ",", "Nov.", "25", ",", "2015", ",", "in", "Chicago", ",", "the", "day", "after", "murder", "charges", "were", "brought", "against", "police", "officer", "Jason", "Van", "Dyke", "in", "the", "killing", "of", "17-year-old", "Laquan", "McDonald", "."], "token_char_offsets": [["792", "794"], ["796", "802"], ["804", "809"], ["811", "818"], ["820", "823"], ["825", "825"], ["827", "829"], ["831", "834"], ["836", "842"], ["844", "849"], ["851", "851"], ["853", "859"], ["861", "865"], ["866", "866"], ["868", "876"], ["877", "877"], ["879", "882"], ["884", "885"], ["886", "886"], ["888", "891"], ["892", "892"], ["894", "895"], ["897", "903"], ["904", "904"], ["906", "908"], ["910", "912"], ["914", "918"], ["920", "925"], ["927", "933"], ["935", "938"], ["940", "946"], ["948", "954"], ["956", "961"], ["963", "969"], ["971", "975"], ["977", "979"], ["981", "984"], ["986", "987"], ["989", "991"], ["993", "999"], ["1001", "1002"], ["1004", "1014"], ["1016", "1021"], ["1023", "1030"], ["1031", "1031"]], "sentence_start": 792, "sentence_end": 1031, "text_entities": [{"entity-type": "GPE", "text": "Chicago", "start": 1, "end": 2}, {"entity-type": "GPE", "text": "Chicago", "start": 22, "end": 23}, {"entity-type": "PER", "text": "man", "start": 6, "end": 7}, {"entity-type": "PER", "text": "officers", "start": 3, "end": 4}, {"entity-type": "PER", "text": "officer", "start": 33, "end": 34}, {"entity-type": "PER", "text": "Laquan McDonald", "start": 42, "end": 44}, {"entity-type": "PER", "text": "Jason Van Dyke", "start": 34, "end": 37}, {"entity-type": "ORG", "text": "police", "start": 2, "end": 3}, {"entity-type": "ORG", "text": "police", "start": 32, "end": 33}], "text_event_mentions": [{"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "trigger": {"start": 8, "end": 9, "text": "custody"}, "arguments": [{"role": "Person", "start": 6, "end": 7, "text": "man"}, {"role": "Agent", "start": 3, "end": 4, "text": "officers"}]}], "text_arguments_flat": [{"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "role": "Person", "start": 6, "end": 7, "text": "man", "mention_index": 0, "arg_index": 0}, {"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "role": "Agent", "start": 3, "end": 4, "text": "officers", "mention_index": 0, "arg_index": 1}], "image_event": {"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "role": {"Person": [{"image_ref": "1", "bbox": [660, 214, 1366, 1630]}], "Agent": [{"image_ref": "1", "bbox": [250, 191, 846, 1630]}, {"image_ref": "1", "bbox": [1212, 240, 1782, 1630]}]}}, "image_arguments_flat": [{"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "role": "Person", "image_ref": "1", "bbox": [660, 214, 1366, 1630], "box_index": 0}, {"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "role": "Agent", "image_ref": "1", "bbox": [250, 191, 846, 1630], "box_index": 0}, {"event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "role": "Agent", "image_ref": "1", "bbox": [1212, 240, 1782, 1630], "box_index": 1}], "meta": {"source": "M2E2_raw_rebuilt", "linked_images_in_text_item": ["VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_0.jpg", "VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_1.jpg", "VOA_EN_NW_2015.11.26.3074855_2.jpg"], "crossmedia_row_index": 0, "crossmedia_event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail", "image_event_type": "Justice:Arrest-Jail"}}
